wellhello.com 2017-06-17

# WellHello | Privacy Info

**Our Commitment to Privacy**

wellhello.com takes your privacy seriously. This Policy is designed to help you understand how we collect, use and safeguard the personal information you provide to us and to assist you in making informed decisions when using wellhello.com (the "site"). Please read it carefully. If you are a wellhello.com member, you may contact us regarding this Privacy Policy by logging in to your account at wellhello.com, clicking on the "Support" tab and using the "Contact Us" feature.

 **Not Intended for Minors**

The content on the site is intended for adults only. No person under 18 is allowed to use this site or to disclose information on this site.

 **Access Information Collected**

 ** _Cookies_**

Like most Web sites, wellhello.com uses cookies. A “cookie” is a small piece of data that a Web site stores in a designated file on your computer. Cookies are commonly used to store user names and/or passwords to facilitate access to the site. Cookies can also be used to store, among other things, user preferences, login dates and times, and content viewing history. When you visit a Web site, that site can access only that information which it stored in a cookie — not information put in a cookie by other Web sites. Cookies make your online experience easier and more personalized.

wellhello.com uses cookies and other technologies to recognize you and to provide personalization, as well as to help us understand how our site is used. Users must have cookies enabled in order for the site to function properly.

Cookies help wellhello.com and its affiliates and advertisers track users\' activities for the purpose of counting and crediting views, clicks, referrals and purchases. The cookies themselves tell wellhello.com nothing about the user personally. wellhello.com also lets other companies that show advertisements on some of our pages set and access their cookies on your computer. Other companies’ use of their cookies is subject to their own privacy policies, not this one.

 ** _Server Log and Clickstream Data_**

Our site\'s servers also automatically identify your computer by its Internet Protocol address (a unique string of numbers that is assigned to your computer by your Internet Service Provider) each time you access the site, and maintain logs of the specific content on the site that you access. Our servers also record various information pertaining to your computer configuration, including but not limited to the Web browser software you use, the resolution settings of your monitor, and the Web site from which you were referred to the site, if any.

 **User Information Collected**

Certain functionality of the site is available only to registered users of the site ("Users"). In order to become a User, we require you to supply the following information:

First and last name;  
Email address;  
ZIP Code  
State/Province

We may occasionally ask you to provide other demographic information, such as income and education level. You are not required to provide such information in order to become a User. Such information is treated in the same manner as the User Information identified above.

We require you to select a unique user name. Please note that your user name is not "User Information" for the purpose of this privacy policy, and will be visible to other users of the site (for example, to identify you as the author of certain posts, or in a list of Users logged in at a given time). Accordingly, if you do not wish to disclose your identity to others on the site, you should select a user name that does not include any personally identifiable information.

Users may upload content including posts, comments on others\' posts, and audiovisual works. This Privacy Policy does not apply to information contained in, or ascertainable from, the content you upload to the site. By uploading content to the site, you waive any claim to privacy rights in connection with information contained in, or ascertainable from, such content.

 **How We Use the Information Collected**

 ** _Providing Information and Services_**

We use the User Information to contact you about changes to our site, new services, features or products we offer, or other information we think you will find of interest, as well as to customize your user experience. We may also disclose or provide User Information to our affiliates, agents and service providers, for the purpose of providing you with offers and information. By signing up as a User of the Site and agreeing to receive emails from this Site, you are agreeing that we may disclose and transfer your email address and all other personal information you supply to our affiliates, agents or service providers.

wellhello.com is a direct marketer that delivers email messages to its subscribers. When working with its merchants, wellhello.com reserves the right to review and edit outgoing messages to ensure messages are delivered to subscribers. Users may unsubscribe to electronic mailings sent by us at any time by following the instructions contained at the end of every wellhello.com newsletter or mailing. Users wishing to unsubscribe from wellhello.com messages can also send a message to [info@wellhello.com](mailto://info@wellhello.com).

We will not rent, sell, or share your personally identifiable information (i.e., your name or email address) with other people or non-affiliated companies except to provide products or services you’ve requested, when we have your permission, or under the following circumstances:

  * We respond to subpoenas, court orders, or other legal process, or to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims.
  * We believe it is necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activity, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of wellhello.com\'s terms of use, or as otherwise required by law.
  * We transfer information about you if wellhello.com is acquired by or merged with another company, or in connection with a potential acquisition or merger.

 ** _Serving Advertising_**

We may disclose non-personally identifiable information about user habits, characteristics and user patterns, based on aggregate user statistics, to others in connection with the advertising, marketing, or operation of our site. In addition, we may display targeted advertisements based on your User Information. Advertisers (including ad serving companies) may assume that people who interact with, view, or click targeted ads meet the targeting criteria—for example, men ages 35-40.

wellhello.com does not provide any personal information to the advertiser when you interact with or view a targeted ad. However, by interacting with or viewing an ad you are consenting to the possibility that the advertiser will make the assumption that you meet the targeting criteria used to display the ad.

 ** _Web site Administration / R &D_**

We use non-personally identifiable information to gather data about our users and to enhance and design our site to make it easier, faster and friendlier to use. Additionally, Access Information helps us know how many people visit our site, when they visit and how they use our service. We may disclose this data to others in the aggregate in connection with sales, marketing, development, or other activities.

 **Your Ability to Edit Your Account Information and Preferences**

You can update your email address through the account settings page. If you desire not to receive information about products or services we think may be of interest, you can change the notification options in your account settings.

We reserve the right to send you certain communications relating to the site, such as service announcements, administrative messages and newsletters, without offering you the opportunity to opt out of receiving them.

 **Confidentiality and Security**

wellhello.com employs industry standard security measures to ensure the security of all data. Access to wellhello.com customer data is accessible via password protection through the Advertiser and Publisher Accounts created by each Advertiser and Publisher, and to designated wellhello.com employees who require system level access in order to perform their jobs. Access to data that identifies a User\'s name and/or e-mail addresses is limited to designated wellhello.com employees who require such access in order to perform their jobs and to an Advertiser or Publisher that provided such information. Each Advertiser and Publisher is responsible for maintaining the confidentiality of its own password used for accessing its accounts on the wellhello.com Network.

 **Changes to this Privacy Policy**

WE MAY REVISE THIS POLICY AT ANY TIME BY POSTING THE REVISED POLICY ON THE SITE. YOUR CONTINUED USE OF THE SITE FOLLOWING SUCH POSTING INDICATES YOUR ACCEPTANCE OF THE CHANGES.

 **Questions and Suggestions**

If you have questions or suggestions, please email us at privacy@wellhello.com

BY USING THIS SITE, YOU CONSENT TO THE PRACTICES SET FORTH IN THIS POLICY.
